export const QueenslandQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following adaptations do cassowaries possess?",
    answers: [
      "Echolocation abilities",
      "Venomous spines",
      "Hollow bones for buoyancy",
      "Camouflage capabilities",
    ],
    correct: "Hollow bones for buoyancy",
    badge: "cassowary",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the diet of the inland taipan primarily composed of?",
    answers: [
      "Small mammals",
      "Birds and their eggs",
      "Insects and spiders",
      "Aquatic prey, such as fish",
    ],
    correct: "Small mammals",
    badge: "inland-taipan",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the primary habitat of crocodiles?",
    answers: [
      "Dense rainforests",
      "Arctic tundra",
      "Open grasslands",
      "Freshwater and brackish habitats",
    ],
    correct: "Freshwater and brackish habitats",
    badge: "crocodile",
  },
];

export const NorthernTerritoryQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following pythons is native to Australia?",
    answers: [
      "Reticulated python",
      "Burmese python",
      "Green tree python",
      "Ball python",
    ],
    correct: "Green tree python",
    badge: "python",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following species of wallaby is considered the largest?",
    answers: [
      "Agile wallaby",
      "Brush-tailed rock wallaby",
      "Red-necked wallaby",
      "Whiptail wallaby",
    ],
    correct: "Red-necked wallaby",
    badge: "wallaby",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the scientific name of the cane toad?",
    answers: ["Rhinella marina", "Bufo bufo", "Hyla arborea", "Xenopus laevis"],
    correct: "Rhinella marina",
    badge: "cane-toad",
  },
];

export const NSWQuestions = [
  {
    question: "How many stomach compartments do koalas have?",
    answers: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
    correct: "Two",
    badge: "koala",
  },
  {
    question: "What was the Emu War?",
    answers: [
      "A conflict between emus and kangaroos over territory.",
      "A military operation to control the population of emus in Australia.",
      "A sporting event involving emu racing and competition.",
      "A fictional war depicted in a popular Australian novel.",
    ],
    correct:
      "A military operation to control the population of emus in Australia.",
    badge: "emu",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following Australian bandicoot species is considered critically endangered?",
    answers: [
      "Brightly colored abdomen",
      "Long, slender legs",
      "Prominent fangs",
      "Large, intricate webs",
    ],
    correct: "Eastern barred bandicoot",
    badge: "funnel-web",
  },
];

export const VICQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following Australian possum species is known for its gliding ability?",
    answers: [
      "Greater glider",
      "Sugar glider",
      "Ringtail possum",
      "Common brushtail possum",
    ],
    correct: "Sugar glider",
    badge: "possum",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the unique adaptation of wombats that helps them defend against predators?",
    answers: [
      "Sharp claws for climbing trees",
      "Camouflage fur patterns",
      "Ability to emit toxic secretions",
      "Powerful rear end and solid bony plates",
    ],
    correct: "Powerful rear end and solid bony plates",
    badge: "wombat",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is a distinctive physical feature of male Sydney funnel-web spiders?",
    answers: [
      "Northern brown bandicoot",
      "Brush-tailed bettong",
      "Eastern barred bandicoot",
      "Long-nosed bandicoot",
    ],
    correct: "Eastern barred bandicoot",
    badge: "bandicoot",
  },
];

export const SAQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following statements about echidnas is correct?",
    answers: [
      "Capable of regenerating lost limbs",
      "Exceptional hearing abilities",
      "Prehensile tail for gripping branches",
      "One of the few egg-laying mammals",
    ],
    correct: "One of the few egg-laying mammals",
    badge: "echidna",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a distinctive feature of platypus?",
    answers: [
      "Ability to fly short distances",
      "Long, prehensile tail",
      "Venomous spurs on their hind legs",
      "Highly developed echolocation abilities",
    ],
    correct: "Venomous spurs on their hind legs",
    badge: "platypus",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the gestation period of kangaroos?",
    answers: ["2 months", "6 months", "12 months", "18 months"],
    correct: "18 months",
    badge: "kangaroo",
  },
];

export const WAQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Quokkas are endemic to which specific island in Australia?",
    answers: [
      "Kangaroo Island",
      "Fraser Island",
      "Rottnest Island",
      "Tasmania",
    ],
    correct: "Rottnest Island",
    badge: "quokka",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Where is the primary breeding and rookery location for Australian sea lions?",
    answers: [
      "Ningaloo Coast",
      "Sydney Harbour",
      "Kangaroo Island",
      "Christmas Island",
    ],
    correct: "Kangaroo Island",
    badge: "sea-lion",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the average number of teeth a great white shark can have in its mouth at any given time?",
    answers: ["50", "100", "300", "500"],
    correct: "300",
    badge: "great-white",
  },
];

export const TAZQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following statements about huntsman spiders is correct?",
    answers: [
      "Venomous and pose a significant threat to humans",
      "Aggressive behavior and frequent biting",
      "Elaborate webs to catch their prey",
      "Large size and swift movements",
    ],
    correct: "Large size and swift movements",
    badge: "huntsman",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the main threat to the survival of Tasmanian devils in the wild?",
    answers: [
      "Devil facial tumor disease",
      "Loss of habitat due to deforestation",
      "Competition with other carnivorous mammals",
      "Overhunting by humans",
    ],
    correct: "Devil facial tumor disease",
    badge: "taz-devil",
  },
  {
    question:
      "When was the last confirmed sighting of a thylacine in the wild?",
    answers: ["1920s", "1940s", "1960s", "1980s"],
    correct: "1920s",
    badge: "thylacine",
  },
];
